SORFINA AMRAN

RESEARCH ANALYST

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Project management Team management Market research Networking expert Collaborative nature Marketing Campaign Generating Leads

SOFTWARE, PERSONAL & INSTRUMENTS SKILLS

HTML & CSS
Aspen Hysis Software
Avogrado Software
GROMACS Software
PyMOL Software
Microsoft office suite

Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Motivated
Coaching and Mentoring
Professional Communication skill

NMR Inst FT-IR & UV-VIS Inst

CONTACT

- Bangsar, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia
- sorfina.utp@gmail.com No Tel : 018 292 4213

PROFILE

Sorfina had experienced as **Research Analyst** in manufacturing, Oil and gas Industry and conferences summits and corporate marketing events. She also equipped herself with **technical background** for Engineering sector and Applied chemistry.

As for example, Laboratory skill including it's instrument such as (HPLC, FT-IR and UV-Vis). Ultimately, Sorfina always and stay resilient to adapt with new cutting edge technology to add value to her skill such as Coding Language (HTML & CSS).

EXPERIENCE

RESEARCH EXECUTIVE

Marcus Evans Group | Feb 2020 - April 2020

- Analyzed and identify target client contacts based on events topic and geographic markets.
- Developed and improve client contacts information by conducting internet research through Linkedin and others platform based on KPI 60 contacts per day.
- Developed Marketing Campaign based on project given.
- Leveraged highly effective communication and active listening skills to work effectively with diverse backgrounds and accomplish common research goals.
- Provide an idea and work closely with sales manager and senior manager to discuss the project operation.

EXPERIENCE

RESEARCH ANALYST

BSL Technologies Sdn Bhd | April 2019 - Feb 2020

- Created and maintain marketing materials for sales presentation and client meeting while work closely with sales engineer.
- Created and prepared slide presentation for Managing Director and Sale Director that focus in Manufacturing Sector.
- Created a documentation outlining research findings for use by project managers and customer to make an accurate decision about future plan.
- Contribute ideas to concept development strategic planning and business operation.

SORFINA AMRAN

RESEARCH ANALYST

EXPERIENCE

PROJECT SALES ENGINEER

BSL Technologies Sdn Bhd | July 2019 - Aug 2019

- Involved in centralization project for Plastic manufacturing Industry.
- Prepared cost estimates by studying plans, and related customer documents,
- Prepared and delivered technical presentations explaining product or service to customer.
- Conferred with customers and engineers to assess equipment needs and to determine system requirement.
- Recommend improved materials or machinery to customers, showing how changes will lower costs or increase production.
- Prepared sales engineering reports by collecting, analyzing, and summarizing sales information and application trends.
- Prepared Quotation and Project Proposal
- Experienced how to use an Autocad

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN APPLIED CHEMISTRY

UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI PETRONAS | 2015 - 2018

- Accredited By Royal Society of Chemistry United Kingdom
- Best student in Applied Chemistry 2018
- Final Year Project Award (Bronze), awarded by PETRONAS CEO
- Science & Engineering Design Exhibition (Silver)
- Dean's List



DIPLOMA IN CHEMICAL ENGINEERING TECHNOLOGY (ENVIRONMENT)

UNIVERSITI KUALA LUMPUR (MICET)| 2011- 2014

Dean's List



FINAL YEAR PROJECT UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI PETRONAS

Final Year Project 2018: THESIS TITLE - An Insight into Solubility of Hydrogen Sulphide in Protic Ionic Liquid (PILs) from Computer Simulation

- 5 Protic Ionic Liquids (PILs) were used to study it's efficiency of removing Hydrogen sulfide by replacing it's conventional solvent (Amine) with a method of Molecular Dynamic (MD) simulation and Bennet Acceptance Ratio (BAR).
- Density, Interaction energy (IE) and the present of amine group in PILs are the contributing factors in it's solubility.
- Overall result shows that, by weakening the IE and by presenting the amine functional group contribute to the most solubility of Hydrogen sulfide in PILs







